# **Andrew Nater**

#### **SUMMARY**

Over a decade of experience designing, developing, and maintaining software for businesses in health, education, and hospitality. Track record of successfully building reliable software, managing projects and leading teams. Thrives in collaborative, high trust, low ego environments.

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Arts, Digital Media, University of Central Florida, 2015

Associate in Arts, General Studies, Valencia College, 2012

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Fuzzy Pet Health | Software Engineering Manager | October 2021 - Today

I managed full stack engineers on Fuzzy's internal tools team. My team built and maintained the admin UI for veterinary records & customer support; membership & subscription services; and integrations with platforms handling e-commerce (Shopify), inventory fulfillment (Vetsource), customer support (Zendesk), and marketing (Iterable). I contributed improvements to the hiring process, code challenges, and career progression process. I reported to the VP of Engineering.

Stack: Typescript, React, Redux, Taildwind CSS; Ruby, Rails, Sidekig; Redis, Postgres

### Fuzzy Pet Health | Lead Software Engineer | April 2021 – October 2021

I led the redesign of Fuzzy's iOS and Android apps. The redesign improved performance and user engagement, contributing to a successful series C round of funding. I wrote and reviewed code and system architecture documents for web, iOS, and Android projects. I worked closely with product managers, designers, and executives to capture technical requirements and set expectations for project delivery.

Stack: iOS, Swift; Android, Kotlin; Ruby, Rails, Sidekiq; Redis, Postgres

## Silversheet, AMN Healthcare | Senior Software Engineer | April 2020 - April 2021

I led a team of full-stack software engineers maintaining a medical credentialing SaaS serving hundreds of healthcare businesses and thousands of providers. We practiced Test Driven Development and Continuous Integration & Delivery. I ran daily stand-ups, sprint planning and retrospectives. I worked with product managers, QA, and senior leadership to estimate and plan projects. I became a sprint team lead in my first 6 months. I helped introduce code coverage requirements to our code approval process, increasing average test coverage on new code to 94%.

Stack: Slim templates, Javascript, React; Ruby, Rails, Sidekiq; Redis, Postgres

# **Andrew Nater**

### Full Sail University | Front-end Developer | May 2018 - April 2020

I maintained the front-end for a learning management system serving thousands of students and faculty. I collaborated with product managers, business analysts, and UX designers to capture and implement requirements. I participated in code review, estimation & planning, and interviewing. I introduced front-end testing. I improved the app's overall accessibility for student's with vision impairments. I built prototypes for new projects, including a React Native app and an analytics server. I developed the front-end interview code challenges and on-boarding documentation.

Stack: React, Redux, Immutable.js, Jest

## Wellness | Co-founder, Designer, Developer | June 2017 - April 2020

I co-created and maintained Wellness, a mental health app for iOS. I handled a variety of tasks, from customer support and bug fixes to releasing App Store builds and analyzing sales figures. I built our app server and marketing website. I developed UI for the iOS app. I designed UI for the iOS app and marketing materials with Sketch and Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, After Effects, Illustrator).

Stack: iOS, Swift, Objective-C; Typescript, React, Node.js, Express; Firebase

## Wyndham Vacation Ownership | Software Engineer | January 2016 – June 2017

I maintained and documented front-end code for a suite of internal and customer-facing web applications. Code was version controlled with TFS. I documented requirements with Microsoft Office suite. I designed wireframes, user experience diagrams, and user interfaces with Adobe Creative Suite. I conducted code reviews, attended daily stand ups (SCRUM), and provided direction to the offshore development team.

Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, React

### Trim Media | Co-founder, Designer, Developer | May 2012 - April 2016

I developed responsive websites for clients using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. I wrote back end code in PHP, Ruby, and Node.js. I managed web hosting and domain registration for clients with various providers. I designed brand collateral, stationary, graphics, wireframes, user experience flows, and websites. I conducted design reviews and usability testing. Deliverables were created with Adobe Creative Suite.

# Apple | Genius (Mac Technician) | July 2010 - May 2015

I provided customer support, troubleshooting, and hardware repairs for Apple Mac, iPhone, iPad, and iPod products. I maintained above-average customer satisfaction (NPS) scores. I collaborated with coworkers and leadership to develop key initiatives that improved the customer and employee experience. I also provided training and mentorship to coworkers.